This is the Inclusive Certification Coach —
an accessibility-first learning coach for enterprise teams.
It's built as eight cooperating agents, grounded in
Microsoft Foundry IQ, with every claim cited.
The clean landing page invites the learner
to set a goal and build a plan.
Three tabs sit at the top:
Learn, Manager view, and How it works.
In the sidebar I pick my certification — AZ-204 —
my role, and how I work best.
I note ADHD and trouble focusing,
then choose Build my plan.
The Curator retrieves grounded content
and builds a cited learning path.
Each module shows recommended hours,
an accommodation note, and its source citation.
Behind it, the Study Plan Generator schedules
short, focus-friendly blocks with breaks.
Every step is grounded in retrieved knowledge-base
chunks — no hallucinated facts.
With Listen mode on, the Accessibility Narrator
turns the result into a spoken script.
There's a real player — play, pause,
choose a voice, and adjust the speed.
Symbols and abbreviations are read as words,
so it's screen-reader friendly.
Next, the Calendar Negotiator fits
study into my real week.
It finds genuine gaps between meetings
and books study blocks into them.
I can adjust the daily cap, block length,
and preferred time — it re-books instantly.
If the week is too full, it pushes back with
evidence instead of pretending it fits.
Now the readiness check —
and I choose how I'm tested.
I can pick exactly which topics
to be quizzed on, and how many questions.
The questions are realistic, exam-style
scenarios — not trivia about the guide.
Or I can switch to Teach-it-back and
explain a concept in my own words.
It grades my understanding, names what
I covered, and flags what's missing.
Then it asks one Socratic follow-up
aimed at the biggest gap.
Let me answer the quick questions
and submit them.
The Assessment Agent scores me
and reports my weak areas.
Then the Orchestrator reasons over my
score, weak areas, and attempt history.
It decides one of three actions: advance,
loop back, or escalate to a human.
Here it loops me back — to study
only the areas I got wrong.
One click starts a focused refresher,
re-quizzing just those topics.
The loop is real reasoning,
not a fixed script.
If I need support, the Advocate drafts
a note to my manager for me.
I choose whether to share my accessibility
profile — it's private by default.
Redaction is enforced in code, so the
model can't leak what it never saw.
The draft shows exactly what it shares
and what it keeps private.
Nothing is sent without my approval.
The Manager view rolls the whole team
up for a people manager.
Manager Insights reasons over each learner's
progress against the readiness threshold.
Profiles of learners who haven't opted in
stay redacted here too.
Finally, How it works
makes the reasoning legible.
It logs every agent step, the chunks it
retrieved, and their relevance scores.
And it shows the orchestrator's signals
weighed and alternatives rejected.
Deterministic guardrails keep it safe —
stalled learners always reach a human.
Grounded, reliable, and accessibility-first —
backed by 72 of 72 eval checks.
Thanks for watching.